Presenter: Good evening. Welcome to Quiz Night.
Tonight’s show comes from Manchester.
And our first contestant is Eddie from Manchester.
Hi, Eddie. Are you nervous?
Eddie: No, not really. I think I’m, er, well prepared.
Presenter: Well, let’s hope so. The rules are the same as always.
I’m going to read you some sentences, and you have ten seconds to say
if the sentence is true or false.
If you get the first answer right, you win one hundred pounds.
Then for each correct answer, you double your money, so if you get the second answer right,
you win two hundred pounds, and for the third correct answer, you win four hundred pounds.
For eight correct answers, you win twelve thousand eight hundred pounds.
But if you get an answer wrong, you lose all the money.
Remember, you can also phone a friend, so if you’re not sure about one of the answers,
you can phone your friend to help you.
Is that OK, Eddie?
Eddie: Yeah, OK.